and we are back this is lee's [__] and
i'm here with my host john kiriakou
and by the way if you have a terrestrial
radio
and you enjoy a boombox something like
that a filco
as i used to have my mustang well here's
another question john before we get to
caleb
real quick what was your first car mine
was a 71 mustang convertible
what was your first car joe oh yeah my
mine was a 72 dodge charger special
edition
oh a mopar guy yeah it was fabulous
i think about it a lot my brother
started out as a ford guy
like me but he's become a mopar guy
and i can't i can't really argue with
that you know what i mean like there's
nothing
sure and the new the new chargers
are as close as we have in this day and
age to a muscle car those are nice
oh yeah they are the chargers and the
challengers
really really cool cars yeah yeah the
challenger challenger's great too
joining us now caleb open we love having
cantaloupe on the show
he of course is an arty correspondent
and an author
hey caleb how you doing today i'm great
how about yourself
how both are you doing good to talk to
you yeah
we're good yeah i'm good john you're
good right
yeah i'm doing well thank you okay so
caleb
we were just talking about this with
alexander mccorris it was very
interesting to me
that china literally like within an
hour after the inauguration i think it
must have been
like within an hour after the
inauguration they announced sanctions
against 28 people including
mike pompeo the ex the
barely ex secretary of state he still
had the secretary of state
skank stank on him from uh just just
being secretary of state
there was maybe a skank too i don't know
not getting in his personal life
but the chinese sanctioned him
and a bunch of other people including
the newly pardoned steve bannon
and uh we were talking about that with
alexander what was your take on that
caleb
well it seems like china which has
pulled ahead
amid this global pandemic while
economies around the world are
not expanding there certainly was and
they
you know experienced at least some rate
of growth in 2020.
uh they're saying look you can sanction
us and we can sanction you back
and why not make a symbolic gesture and
go after
some of the people that have accused us
of allegations that are widely disputed
uh that have been funding uh groups in
hong kong that have been engaging in
provocative acts of street violence
lighting people on fire uh etc
and uh on top of that since mike pompeo
really made his twitter page
just you know a a festival of
anti-chinese uh
hysteria why not uh you know make a
statement as he
heads out of office that they don't
particularly care much for that
um and i think it's also to send a
message
if you listen to biden's speech you know
biden was very very
very much repudiating the previous four
years it was probably a gesture to buy
look the past four years are over you
don't like the guys who came before you
neither do we
uh so maybe that's something we have in
common and maybe we can sit down and
resolve this
and and end this trade war and reach a
conclusion
uh where we can have better relations
between the two countries and yes you
talked a tough game against us during
the elections and yes you're not
beijing biden you're not a communist
you're not sympathizing with china but
you know maybe we can
restart all of this um and uh we don't
like the trump guys either
so let's let's negotiate i mean sounds
like to me that's what the jester said
that's very interesting you know i i
heard too
some messages in biden's speech today
about human rights he didn't come right
out and address the issue as a separate
issue
but it was sort of this blanket um
oh re-commitment i guess to to
long-standing american policy on human
rights
uh and that made me think of the news
that we've seen over the previous
i don't know year or two about the
uyghurs in western china
the united nations says that there's a
genocide there
uh the chinese say there is no such
uh genocide going on that this is uh
an uprising it's a national security
issue
where should we expect the biden people
caleb to
fall on the issue of the uyghurs do you
foresee any
kind of change in u.s policy toward
china because of this
i don't think the u.n said that there
was a genocide i think there were
certain countries
within the united nations who used their
platform at the u.n
to make that allegation but there were
many countries at the u.n who did not
agree with that allegation
and not just china not just russia but
many countries around the world
didn't buy that allegation but certainly
that allegation is being made by a
number of u.s alliance countries
um but there are a number of countries
that are you know sympathetic to china
and russia a number of countries that
are just kind of
neutral you know like india and other
countries that are saying and we don't
quite buy that
um but look human rights has become the
mantra
of u.s military policy used to be we
were going around the world to fight the
communists because you know you know the
vietnamese were going to get in their
canoes and
come over here and and invade the united
states and you know
abolish our american way of life and so
we had to stop the domino theory or
whatever
now uh you know the pentagon is just uh
superman
uh and wherever uh superman hears people
around the world being oppressed why
uh he jumps into the nearest phone booth
and puts on his pentagon
superman costume and flies into action
to rescue the oppressed and
anywhere in the world and uh you know
the united states is just a great
superhero and the pentagon is nothing
but this humanitarian rescue
organization that goes around saving
people all over the planet
that's the narrative we get uh people
say that really
probably started you know being the
dominant justification for us military
interventions with the clinton
administration
and yugoslavia right there was no no no
perception that that
serbia and slovakia were in any way a
threat to the united states
but the united states had to intervene
because it was just this moral
obligation
then the rest of the world looks at this
and says really you are so concerned
about human rights in certain select
countries but you're aligned with saudi
arabia
and you're aligned with all kinds of
brutal dictatorships in south and
central america
and you've got all kinds of brutal human
rights violating regimes that you
not only are friendly with but give
weapons and money to
and something's not right about this
narrative but that's not the way it goes
on cnn and uh
and this is how it always goes and this
is kind of an interesting aspect of how
the liberal narrative has triumphed it
used to be you know we were fighting the
reds and the commies and
and communism had to stop from expanding
now it's the united states is this
purveyor of
liberal values all around the world and
we have this global responsibility to
to bring liberal ideas to all these
countries around the world and and
it's kind of a change in the narrative
and i think this may be what some of the
trump allies were talking about when
they talked about globalism
the trump folks were just as much in
favor of military interventionism at
least the pompeo and
gina haspel crowd um but they seemed to
justify it more in terms of the
interests of the u.s population overall
not this kind of global human rights
narrative
lee this is uh an important point and i
i
i'd love to hear your thoughts too uh
this is an important point that caleb
makes because
there really is a double standard there
really is hypocrisy
in u.s foreign policy especially on the
issue of human rights
you know every embassy every u.s embassy
in the world
every u.s embassy in every country with
which we have diplomatic relations
every year is tasked with writing a
human rights report on that country and
submitting it to
congress i was the human rights officer
in in bahrain for two years i wrote that
report it's quite an
undertaking and it usually goes for
hundreds and hundreds of pages
so we like to we like to pretend that
we're a shining beacon
of human rights yet we
provide arms and uh and aid to countries
run by dictators
we have this special relationship with
the likes of
saudi arabia for example and and many
other
countries that are run by dictators uh
we have a death penalty of our own uh
here in this country
and then we criticize other countries
for doing exactly the same kind of thing
that we do is that going to change let
me let me give you the
let me give you this the other side of
exactly the same coin
because i agree with what both you guys
are saying but i'm gonna bring up a
what sounds at first like a completely
different point
but it's actually the same thing so
somebody who i worked for steve bannon i
wrote for breitbart for many years
people on the right
you don't hear people at the right as
they get together talk about human
rights
i'm just telling you i you know if if
you're at cpac
walking around there's not a lot of
discussion
either up on the stage or just at the
open bars at night about
hey you know i'm really worried about
human rights no one talks about that
just so i'm just saying it's just not
topic of discussion
but you know what has been a big topic
of discussion
for a few years is radical islamic
terrorism
and you hear that up on the stage and
people talking about it people
on the right are concerned about radical
islamic terrorism in fact
when trump first came into office he
made a point of saying look the media
won't say radical
islamic terrorism and i'll say it over
and over again
he kind of stopped doing that this is
the same issue
here's the hypocrisy if i was at
breitbart
and breitbart had decided under bannon
to be we're really going to be pro-china
i could have done article after article
after
article about radical islamic terrorism
in china by the uyghurs
that right that's what the issue there
is and i'm not even trying to take a
side
but it's not like just the chinese
decided we don't like you
there is a real problem with terrorism
in that region and what
what they did was they've gotten think
about this
it's amazing because i've seen it on the
right
they've gotten right wing people who
five years ago
were talking about the muslim
brotherhood and all this other stuff and
they didn't even know what they were
talking about
because they didn't know that the muslim
world league was a bigger deal
they've got them to take up the plight
of the uyghurs
as part of their new cold war narrative
on china so
on the left i agree with you they talk
about human rights
and they're hypocrites and hypocrites
completely
but in the right they no longer talk
about
radical islamist terrorism certainly as
it relates to china so
uh caleb i'm curious about what both you
have to say about that
caleb take it well what's interesting is
i think
big new brzezinski would be absolutely
delighted
with this inauguration and with this new
administration
zbigniew brzezinski considered himself
to be kind of a mentor to barack obama
there's connections there with the
columbia university center of communist
studies where obama
obama studied at columbia and that's
where brzezinski's kind of you know
academic following was and that this big
new brzezinski his whole strategy for
the cold war is he said let's
make the cold war less ideological let's
downplay this capitalism versus
communism stuff
and instead let's you know find people
in the communist world and find people
in the east that can be allies and
and we can use this kind of proxies and
let's play up the differences
among the soviet eastern bloc and
between china and the ussr and let's
let's covertly manipulate uh potential
rivals the united states
against each other and it was victory
brzezinski who bragged about
the afghan trap and how the soviet union
was lured into afghanistan
and how the united states worked with a
wealthy young saudi by the name of osama
bin laden
to build an army of extremists
in afghanistan to fight against the
people's democratic republic
um and they eventually won and that's
where the taliban came from
what's interesting is that china at that
point you know was being courted by the
united states as an ally against the
soviets and in the
uigar regions uh that's where osama bin
laden
and the uscia and others set up shop
on china's border with afghanistan and
that's why
there is a base of jihadist and wahhabi
extremism in that region it mainly comes
from the fact that
that china allowed the uscia and others
to to set up
those kind of networks there to fight
the soviets in afghanistan
uh so the legacy of brzezinski the
legacy of kind of
courting different extremist and radical
groups around the world utilizing them
as proxies against our geopolitical
rivals
uh that legacy is very very well alive
and i think that's why
you know on the right there was this
whole thing you know you know why will
obama never say radical islamic terror
because he's a secret obama wasn't a
muslim but it was about the fact that
the united states was actively courting
people in places like libya
and syria to be proxies of american
intelligence to tear down the
the government of libya which had the
highest life expectancy on the african
continent to tear down and
format civil war in syria which has cost
us at least half a million lives if not
more than that
um and that you know if obama were to
get up and talk about radical islamic
terrorism that would offend these
various wahhabi and muslim brotherhood
aligned groups
that were being utilized as as proxies
to fight our battles for us and tear
down
nationalist and socialist and
anti-imperialist governments that we
don't particularly care for
um and i think that that brzezinski uh
brzezinski's ghost and brzezinski's
legacy is very very well alive
and the democrats are very much out of
that out of that tradition of foreign
policy strategy
true you know it's funny too that these
foreign policies which
which ought to be controversial and
ought to be uh
the cause of great debate on capitol
hill are not
and they just continue regardless of
who's in the white house regardless of
what party is in control of either the
white house or the congress
and they go for generations it's the
same thing
year after year after year and then we
find ourselves in these endless wars
yeah what's interesting is i i become
keenly aware
of how and by the way brzezinski is
listed in the little
ukraine's little black book that i have
by the way i'll just say he's one of the
names in there
uh what i noticed and i became
keenly aware of it recently is how
bannon himself specifically
was involved in ginning up these
point counterpoint narratives kind of
brilliantly
where he was working with white
nationalists
period but he's also really
uh has fealty to zionists too
and that seems like a contradiction at
first but that's what
that's what bannon was doing so that
brzezinski thing you're talking about
caleb i mean it sounds like you know in
a way
people don't appreciate what a skilled
offer i really mean this
operator bannon is
because he was able to work stuff behind
the scenes
he's his main audience is on the right
but he's ginning up these divisions
which is a tried and true technique go
ahead go ahead caleb well well
i just wanted to add one difference that
i think is
very key between the democrats and the
republicans or the the left and the
so-called right or the so-called
laughter
you know that one of the differences is
kind of how they want the united states
to
be perceived not so much about what the
united states
does around the world but rather how the
united states is perceived what kind of
friendly gestures are made or not made
etc um one key difference is that you
know john brennan who was obama's cia
director
made a really big point of saying the
cia would never torture uh they did not
believe in torture if obama ever asked
him to torture he would resign
well you know when trump came in john
brennan was out
um and first we had mike pompeo and then
he moved on to be secretary of state and
then gina haspel
who has a reputation for being a
defender of torture and
harsh interrogation techniques uh she
stepped up to leave the cia and then you
know of course she has stepped down and
biden will be replacing her and it
wasn't so much an attitude
a question of should the usa torture or
not i think the issue at hand is should
the united states be perceived as a
country that tortures
and on the right uh there's a feeling
that we should be known as a strong
country you mess with us we might
torture you
we don't care if you like us we don't
care if you're friendly but you mess
with us
be afraid peace through strength on the
left there's this attitude that we
should be perceived as this woke
human rights loving country that is is
you know getting over it racial
injustice and intolerance
and it's really a matter of emphasis
what narrative should united the united
states put out there an image of peace
through strength be terrified of us
work with us or be afraid or you know uh
look we're this amazing human rights
loving free society and we want to bring
some of that freedom to you and wouldn't
it be fun to work with us we're really
really friendly
uh good cop bad cop almost well okay we
got to go to a quick break here
when we john when we come back you bring
it back
and i'm very curious about what you have
to say about what caleb said
and i will see caleb's interesting point
and raise it
you know half a chip because caleb's
pretty damn smart so i can't
really out bet him but i'm very curious
john
you being inside the c.i.a did you
see that dynamic in rank and file
ci just the people the guy at the next
desk or the guy
the next desk did you see that did you
see people
who were on the right on the i mean
legitimately
not playing a role but you talk to him
because i heard back in the early days
of the cia
i've read i read more books about that
there was the sort of
ivy league educated group
and then there's the people who kind of
ex-cops xcia people
and that was one cultural split within
the cia
we'll find out about that and more
hitler malphine
is our guest and of course i'm joined by
my co-host
the esteemed john kiriakou i'm lee
stranahan this
is the back story
uh
welcome back to the back story i'm john
kiriakou i'm here with my co-host
lee stranahan we were talking liam a
moment ago about uh with caleb about um
uh the attitude at the cia the attitude
of the racket
among the rank and file to
to torture and you know it's it's kind
of funny when i was there
in uh 2002 at the very start of the
torture program
there were so few people who were read
into the compartment
that when i was first read into it there
were only 16 people
in the entire us government who even
knew that there was a torture program
now of course that that changed little
by little
in the intervening months i'm talking
about uh
the summer of 2002 and i can tell you
that there was a big
difference between the rank and file and
the cia's leadership
uh the rank and file thought this was a
terrible idea
that first of all it stained us it
dragged us down
to the level of the people we were
trying to fight
but at the leadership level there was
this
there was this desire for revenge
because
they had dropped the ball 9 11 happened
on
their watch this was the worst
intelligence failure in the history of
the united states
three thousand americans died that day
because
they didn't do their jobs and so
whether torture worked or not
was not an issue it was not something
that was discussed
at that high level it was torture for
the sake of torture
and if we were able to gather
information that might disrupt a future
attack then that was fine too
but in my view it was just for revenge
it was at the lower level
at my level where people said this is
wrong wrong wrong and we should not be
in the business of doing it
see everybody's shocked into silence we
were all shocked into silence
also there's three of us and we can't
see each other and it's hard knowing to
talk
but caleb you thought comments what john
said there well no i mean it
sounds quite morally reprehensible um
you know when it really gets down to it
and that you know i mean i've heard many
experts say that torture doesn't really
work in terms of getting information the
reason that
governments engage in torture is to
terrify the population and have the
population know
or the enemy know that this is something
that they are capable of doing and that
perhaps the rationale might be that if
folks are not afraid to die
because they are they believe they will
they will go to heaven because they are
martyrs for the faith
uh that they will be terrified of
getting tortured but it really at the
end of the day is a is a
this is a tool of terrifying people it
is a tool
of of you know getting people to submit
and surrender
it's not a tool of gathering useful
intelligence from my understanding would
you say that's correct
that's right and you know another thing
too that i think is very important
reasonable people can agree to disagree
first of all though it's a it's a
scientific fact that torture does not
work
you just can't gather actionable
intelligence because
the person being tortured will tell you
anything that they think you want to
know just to get you to stop
it might be true it's likely not true
but either way the torturer then has to
pass
all that information to a team of
analysts
to vet it and by the time they finish
vetting it
that bomb has gone off in xyz city and
you failed
again now if if you want to torture for
the sake of torture
there are people on the right who think
that this is a viable
option that this is something that's not
morally reprehensible and should be done
but if that's your position you've got
to change the law
because the law is very clear torture is
illegal
you can't just pretend that the law
doesn't exist
you know and forgive me for getting on
my soapbox but
we have a law in this country called the
torture act of 1946 and it
outlawed specifically outlawed exactly
those techniques
that our enemies that we used on our
enemies
after 9 11 like waterboarding for
example i'm going to use waterboarding
as the
as the example because it's the easiest
one well in 1946
we executed japanese soldiers who had
waterboarded american pows we
executed them in january of 1968
the washington post ran a front page
photograph of an american soldier
waterboarding a north vietnamese
prisoner
when that photo ran robert mcnamara the
secretary of defense ordered an
investigation that very same day
that soldier was arrested he was charged
with torture
convicted and sentenced to 20 years in a
military prison
well the law never changed from 1946 to
to 2002 to 2021. the law never changed
we changed but again if
we change we can't just pretend that the
law doesn't exist
indeed now the church the church
committee though did reveal that there
were a lot of
i mean this is not the first time the
cia has engaged in this kind of activity
i mean
this stuff went on during and 70s if i'm
not mistaken right
you're absolutely right all the way up
until 1974.
yeah i know what you know one of the
things that's i'm just going to address
something that's going on in the chat
room john
because there's somebody in there who
and i just i just
locked them because i i'm not a free
speech purist on this point i'm in favor
of stupid
uh i'm opposed to stupid people but
somebody's in there saying
because they know a lot more than you
john that a you're lying
that that that and then they're quoting
this article where you said when you
were
brought on that our boss said uh to
steer clear of 911 truthers
which i i don't know if that's true but
i hope it is
and and the reason why is there's enough
bad stuff about
911 that's absolutely provable
such as the saudi involvement in it and
the the pages that we're missing
that i always think that bad information
and a lot of the
and we i've had whitney webb in the show
we talked about the
dancing israelis story and stuff like
that so we've had stuff that i hear 9 11
people
uh truthers like van jones by the way
talk about uh sometimes on the show
but i would like john you to respond and
kendall i'm curious about how you deal
here's the thing i don't think anyone
could accuse
me or john or caleb
of being establishment shills so the
idea
on here that that we're just going along
with the establishment line
on 9 11. i think it's complex but i
think that there's a lot of
stupid stuff that gets said too and i'm
curious about how you deal with that as
a journalist caleb
but john you want to respond first go
ahead yeah listen
i take it on the chin from 911 truthers
all the time i take it on the chin from
the
from the pro torture crowd and uh
listen i'm sorry but i don't remember
those guys being there when we were
kicking down
doors and taking names so if anybody
wants to challenge me go ahead and
challenge me
that doesn't mean i have to take you
seriously that doesn't mean i have to
take your silly opinion seriously
especially if you're yapping from a chat
room 202 521 13 20 is the number
and i say this all the time and i mean
it call in if you want to say something
don't swear
you know could you know yeah it's a live
show don't swear
act the way your mom would want you to
act on the phone but aside from that
caleb what's your do you i'm curious
about a you're jake in general
on what this 911 truther stuff
that comes up and go ahead caleb
honestly i have questions about
the official story of 911 but that's all
i have because i don't
as a journalist say anything i do not
know and i don't know
anything other than you know what about
the 28 pages
what about saudi involvement yes you
know i i there are other things that i
just wonder about but beyond that you
can't really do anything
and i'm i'm very careful because there
is so much out there about 911 that is
very easy to debunk there are so many
things on the internet that people
allege that are mysterious about 911 and
if you look at them they're not based on
reality you have to be very careful
because if you then repeat any of those
things you're immediately discredited
um and i you know there was a document
that was revealed by
cass sunstein uh who was the husband of
samantha power
um and it talked about you know quote
unquote conspiracy theories being a
threat to national security
and one of the proposed methods of
dealing with these conspiracy theories
that were considered to be a threat to
national security
was what they called cognitive
infiltration and that would be filling
the internet up with other conspiracy
theories
to discredit conspiracy theories and um
i've noticed that you know it seems
weird
after anything happens in the united
states anything
immediately all over the internet it's
declared a false flag
you would think that crimes don't happen
news events don't happen in the united
states anymore
because immediately all over the
internet no matter what happens
immediately uh people are claiming it's
a hoax and that makes me wonder you know
if somebody wanted to really actually
have a hoax
it would no one would notice because no
matter what happens it gets to be
declared a hoax and i think
on the one hand that shows that there's
a huge amount of public distrust of
government that people are ready to
think anything's a hoax number one but i
think it also shows that there's a
there's a bit of a conscious effort to
create a light switch effect where uh
basically you believe
everything mainstream media says or
everything's a false flag and a hoax
done by the reptile people in the
illuminati and you're one of the crazies
and
and that kind of is the dynamic that
they've created either believe
everything mainstream us media says 100
percent
or be alone and obviously the truth is
somewhere in the middle
u.s mainstream media has gotten it wrong
on a number of occasions uh there have
been
lies in american media like weapons of
mass destruction and such
but there was also a lot of a lot of you
know you know very very confused and
delusional people out there you know
putting out their views on the internet
so
you know by creating that light switch
effect we can't really have a
conversation and if you just introduce
the
conspiracy allegation into the
conversation it poisons everything in a
way
no i i agree and it's it's the same as
racism
you know i was talking to uh rabbi yakko
shapiro about this
uh recently you know as i and i've
talked
i've talked about a lot that the fact is
if you talk about soros your
anti-semitic
is a way to avoid conversation about
soros
and on the other hand there is such a
thing as anti-semitism
and so if if i'm talking about
the rothschild's connection to genie
energy and someone jumps in and goes
yeah and they're jews i go i don't know
why i did a southern accent there but
you know it's stereotypical
but ah but because you could be yankee
you could
have any accent hey jews that's fine but
you don't need a southern accent is my
point
but i immediately you've derailed the
conversation
you just took it what what are you doing
and now
let's see how this go actually i know
dave a little bit so
i'm glad he called in i said to people
call in 202 521 1320.
two comment on this topic dave from
california
what is your take sir hello people uh
you you all you all have a fantastic
point about the the nuttiness because
i've heard the the planes didn't exist
and i've heard that there was beams
being fired from satellites and all
kinds of crap
but hey how about how about the pile
drivers that damaged the
destroyed the entire buildings not once
but twice
through the path of most resistance and
then when the dust cleared they were
gone
what happened to the pile drivers the
upper floors they destroyed the
buildings because they
they weren't even in the picture when
the buildings were completely demolished
they were gone
so what happened there that's my
question and that's i'd like to hear you
guys take on that and i'll take it off
the air thanks a lot lee
thanks dave john you want to take that
one caleb you got anything
honest to god that's the first time i've
heard that i i haven't heard
i haven't heard it before my apologies
caleb do you know anything
same yeah i've yeah i've never heard it
either sorry dave
sorry dude you never heard it either and
also that's it's almost like an
engineering question in a way
which i will admit that i'm completely
unqualified i'm not an engineer
and you know that's it but i've actually
never heard that one before
okay well can i can i make one other
comment too
real quickly caleb i'm sorry uh dave
dave made an important point too
i've heard i've heard the same stories
that it was
it was the quote-unquote jews it was the
the saudis it was the space aliens it
was
you know an inside job it was the bush
family it was the chaney family
i've heard all these these crazy stories
uh over the years with that said there
are
a lot of legitimate questions that have
never been answered
you know we could have we could do a
whole show on the 28 pages
we could do a whole show on the saudi
royal family
i'll tell you just one quick anecdote if
we have the time i think we have seven
or eight minutes left
when we captured up as a beta in
pakistan on the night of march 22nd
2002 i confiscated his
diary and he had been
shot and severely wounded and my orders
were to remain at his bedside so i
started leafing through the diary and it
wasn't just a diary
it was a doodle book a sketchbook an
address book
he would jot down notes to himself well
there were
names and cell phone numbers of three
members
of the saudi royal family in that in
that book
and i wrote them down and i sent them to
headquarters
in a cable well headquarters then
contacted the saudi government and said
hey we want to talk to these three
princes because their
their personal information their private
cell phone numbers were in abu zubair's
diary
well before we could speak to them
before we could interview them
or interrogate them uh one died
in a fiery car crash on a highway
in central saudi arabia all by himself
single car crash
one went camping in the desert and
nobody ever saw him again and the third
died of thirst so you know it makes me
wonder
it makes a lot of people wonder what
exactly was the role
of the saudi royal family or was it
rogue elements
of the saudi royal family this is a
question that has never been answered
and nobody ever wanted to pursue it and
also makes a lot of people wonder why
anyone would ever go camping in saudi
arabia but
indeed let's quickly get to uh
greg from kansas city who was the person
in the chat room thanks for calling in
greg
and uh and not just yapping from the
chat room go ahead
yeah you're welcome um by the way the
article i mentioned it's
from the new republic uh profile on
teriyaki and sputnik so anyway by the
way though and what really got me was
the uh
was the line about you know calling from
chevrolet if you remember i've been
trying
for probably close to a year to reach
out and have a dialogue with you lee i
even
talked with your son shane briefly i
tried to coordinate
and to his to his credit he was very
respectful i mean i
i've been for months trying to talk with
you about a number of things ranging all
the way from the actual
roots and the actual um uh what
breitbart actually represents to like
the real steve bannon to a number of
things and
you know you and he ultimately ended up
blocking me on uh
on twitter but i mean we've i've been
trying to have this i love with you for
a while
you know well if i if i i almost never
block people
so if i block to people and by the way
i've been
a i had the same 2020 as everybody else
and i've been going through an
absolutely brutal divorce
and other stuff and so sorry
i just sorry but if i had to block you
on twitter i almost
never blocked people greg well i think
it was over me critiquing your interview
with
david horo with lee by the way and then
i also we critiqued uh
also i was very critical of your uh of
your apologetics for for roger stone as
well but
look i don't want to get into your
private life that's no i'm not in any
way shape or form trying to do that but
i mean i still still think like
i really tried hard to actually
coordinate a real dialogue greg
greg here's here's the problem i got
right now i've got a few minutes left in
the show we got two more callers
so do me a favor call back again
sometime on an open segment
i'm not trying to blow you off now but i
have to blow you off now
so call back again on another segment
and we will handle that 202 521 1320.
metea from australia go ahead hi hi hi
um i would like to ask you about the
ukrainian black poke how are you talking
about it
okay so i i will tell you a family
member and and then i got to go to the
next call
neither alexander or andrea chalup are
mentioned in here but their father
leo chalupa is mentioned and leo chalupa
is somebody who i haven't even talked
about much
but he is right in this uh small number
of contacts
that the ukrainian embassy he's a he's a
i believe a teacher or a researcher and
i believe
at george washington university but it
could be georgetown because it confuses
me because they both have the name
george in them and they're both in dc so
i get confused sometimes
202 521 1320 real quickly tariff we only
got it we only got a few seconds here
what's on your mind okay uh free julian
science we love you man we still
fighting for you uh i was listening to
george gallery earlier today they were
talking about brighton administration um
new deal with um uh iran is not the same
deal with a
barack obama have something totally
different and he was saying that
a bright administration might want um
for the um
iranians to dis disarm from the missiles
to basically destroy the uh long-range
missiles which you know the iranians
ain't gonna do
so that's going to be it make things
worse
you know so you know hopefully we get
peace in the world you know so
so yeah teri thanks for the call let me
just make sure see john i was having to
do basically air traffic control there
because we had so many cars yeah that
was that was tough we had so many
callers
yeah i guess if you mentioned 911 the
phone lines light up i don't know
something like that
let's let's go to the last point how do
you see do you think
john and caleb do you think that biden
is putting a poison pill
in this new iran reset he's sort of
talking about
caleb let's go to you first i think that
trump buried the iran deal
uh when he ripped it up uh when he
assassinated qasim solimani
uh at this point i i really doubt the
supreme leader of
iran is going to allow new negotiations
to take place
i think iran made huge concessions in
geneva and
at this point any any chance of of the
supreme leader of iran
saying okay we're going to go ahead and
negotiate once again with the united
states i just don't think it's going to
happen
okay john because we've only got a few
seconds left go ahead yeah
you know i think that we might have
crossed the point of no return and
i i'm not optimistic even if biden's um
head and heart are in the right place
i i don't expect anything great to
happen okay and it looks like i get the
final word because we're about out of
time
caleb it's always great to have you on
the show the final word is don't go
camping in saudi arabia
that's my advice because i know people
who've had
my kids go camping my older kids and
i've never been like
maybe they'll die of thirst or something
i don't even know
that's a bad string of luck there yeah
who dies of thirst
how does that happen very tricky it is
saudi arabia
i'm lee stranahan joined by my co-host
john kiriakou we'll be back tomorrow
this
is the back story
you